<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eli's Blog</title><link>https://thisismy.blog/</link><description>Recent content on Eli's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 01:10:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thisismy.blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How many things do I own?</title><link>https://thisismy.blog/p/how-many-things-do-i-own/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 01:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thisismy.blog/p/how-many-things-do-i-own/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://thisismy.blog/p/how-many-things-do-i-own/robert-bye-by34glow7wa-unsplash.jpg" alt="Featured image of post How many things do I own?" />&lt;p>In 2015 I moved in with my now husband Robert and in the course of almost 6 years so many things have happened in my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I got married, moved houses 2 times, addopted a dog, had a brief streaming career, discovered I have ADHD, changed jobs and took very serious my life career, which will be the main topics of future post.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Naturally with all these changes in my life and the different focus I had over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve amassed a very diverse amount of stuff that go from lighting sets (my streamer period) to jewelry making equipment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A combination of finding the minimalism trend and trying to manage my own sporadic impulsive buying, Ive made the conscious effort of not too many things, but even so I still find myself surrounded by random mini mountains of stuff around my house, stuff I don&amp;rsquo;t even recognize or use anymore so I decided to make an inventory of how many things I own and only keep what I really like or need.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My husband and I decided this week that we are going to actually gather all of our stuff in a huge pile and see how many things we have around the house and do some some of massive spring cleaning, I undestood that not only my personal belongings but our shared things too needed this sorting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m really eager to see how many things we actually own both as individuals and as a couple, and I hope that by the end of that massive endeavor we have appointed ourselves for I can make the number of things I own no more than one hundred.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Why one hundred? It seems like and arbitrary number and it kinda is, I came across the concept of people living with the minimalism lifestyle reducing their own items to a hundred or less.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I wonder how many things I own and if I really need more than a hundred to live and lead the happy life I imagine.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>